<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<LegacyAlbum>
  <album_format/>
  <album_type/>
  <art/>
  <collections/>
  <countries/>
  <genres/>
  <moods/>
  <originally_available_at>2018-01-01</originally_available_at>
  <posters>
    <item external="True" url="59bda6e16b7ef22a880616bc491441d1" media="com.plexapp.agents.localmedia_4762bec78731265058ffce36b34d29a2c72ac585" sort_order="1" provider="com.plexapp.agents.localmedia"/>
  </posters>
  <producers/>
  <reviews/>
  <styles/>
  <summary>'Astounding. Thrilling. Amazing.'  (Gillian Flynn) 'Unputdownable.'  (Stephen King) 'A dark, twisty confection.'  (Ruth Ware) 'Absolutely gripping.'  (Louise Penny) For listeners of Gillian Flynn and Tana French comes one of the decade's most anticipated debuts, to be published in 36 languages around the world and already in development as a major film from Fox: a twisty, powerful Hitchcockian thriller about an agoraphobic woman who believes she witnessed a crime in a neighboring house. It isn't paranoia if it's really happening...  Anna Fox lives alone - a recluse in her New York City home, unable to venture outside. She spends her day drinking wine (maybe too much), watching old movies, recalling happier times...and spying on her neighbors. Then the Russells move into the house across the way: a father, mother, their teenaged son. The perfect family. But when Anna, gazing out her window one night, sees something she shouldn't, her world begins to crumble? And its' shocking secrets are laid bare. What is real? What is imagined? Who is in danger? Who is in control? In this diabolically gripping thriller, no one - and nothing - is what it seems. Twisty and powerful, ingenious and moving, The Woman in the Window is a smart, sophisticated novel of psychological suspense that recalls the best of Hitchcock.  BONUS: Includes an interview with author A. J. Finn.</summary>
  <tags/>
  <title>The Woman in the Window (Unabridged)</title>
  <tracks>
    <item key="17697" path="tracks\124438524e6a76b075e7a2316763e5b16681bf43">
      <lyrics/>
      <moods/>
      <original_title>A. J. Finn</original_title>
      <tags/>
      <title>The Woman in the Window: A Novel (Unabridged)</title>
    </item>
  </tracks>
</LegacyAlbum>
